[
  {
    "question": "Main character",
    "answer": "Guy Montag"
  },
  {
    "question": "Montag's wife",
    "answer": "Mildred"
  },
  {
    "question": "Last Person killed by Montag",
    "answer": "Captain Beatty"
  },
  {
    "question": "A machine that tries to kill Montag",
    "answer": "The Hound"
  },
  {
    "question": "The book Montag memorized",
    "answer": "Book of Ecclesiastes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Poem that Montag reads",
    "answer": "Dover Beach"
  },
  {
    "question": "Temperature at which paper burns",
    "answer": "451 degrees Farenheit"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most important girl in the story",
    "answer": "Clarisse McClellan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Author of Fahrenheit 451 ",
    "answer": "Ray Bradbury"
  },
  {
    "question": "Number of walls in Mildred's \"family\"",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Clarisse makes Montag question this feeling",
    "answer": "Happiness"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mildred ___, so techies were called. ",
    "answer": "Ate too many sleeping pills"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leader of so-called \"criminals\" ",
    "answer": "Granger"
  },
  {
    "question": "Montag original thoughts on burning",
    "answer": "Pleasing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Montag convinced Faber to help him by...",
    "answer": "Ripping pages out of the Bible"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Hound's weapon",
    "answer": "A procaine needle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name of fireman that Montag reported",
    "answer": "Black"
  },
  {
    "question": "A(n) ___ man is killed instead of Montag",
    "answer": "Innocent"
  }
]
